<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>podcast on aidful.ai 🤝</title><link>https://aidfulai.github.io/categories/podcast/</link><description>Recent content in podcast on aidful.ai 🤝</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aidfulai.github.io/categories/podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Marketing Against the Grain</title><link>https://aidfulai.github.io/pages/marketing-against-the-grain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aidfulai.github.io/pages/marketing-against-the-grain/</guid><description>Podcast from Kipp Bodnar, Kieran Flanagan
If you want to know what&amp;rsquo;s happening now in marketing, what&amp;rsquo;s ahead, and how you can lead the way, this is your podcast! In this weekly show, HubSpot’s CMO and SVP of Marketing, Kipp Bodnar and Kieran Flanagan, share their marketing expertise - unfiltered in the details, the truth, and like nobody tells it to you. Tune in for high-level perspective, conversation, and the occasional argument as they serve up an honest-to-goodness sense of how you can move your business forward!</description></item><item><title>Marketing Against the Grain/This OpenAI Update Is Going To Replace Google Search with Ben Tossell</title><link>https://aidfulai.github.io/pages/marketing-against-the-grain/this-openai-update-is-going-to-replace-google-search-with-ben-tossell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aidfulai.github.io/pages/marketing-against-the-grain/this-openai-update-is-going-to-replace-google-search-with-ben-tossell/</guid><description>Metadata series: Marketing Against the Grain episode: 72
guest: Ben Tossell release-date: 2022-12-16
Mini-summary An AI like ChatGPT is superior in writing a text as you don&amp;rsquo;t have to do the context switch: going to websearch, talking to colleague, &amp;hellip; The user interface is a massive improvement as everything can happen in one application.
AI will change that content is published because it is useful and not because people want users on their sites.</description></item><item><title>Where It Happens</title><link>https://aidfulai.github.io/pages/where-it-happens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aidfulai.github.io/pages/where-it-happens/</guid><description>Podcast from Greg Isenberg
The future of business is community-based. The biggest companies and creators have community at its core. Where It Happens is the show hosted by Greg Isenberg (CEO Late Checkout, Advisor Reddit) that finds the most interesting entrepreneur and creators breaks down how they do it.
Episodes: YouTube Transcribed episodes with highlights and mini-summary: aidful.ai</description></item><item><title>Where It Happens/How Writers Can Be More Productive Using AI with Ben Tossell</title><link>https://aidfulai.github.io/pages/where-it-happens/how-writers-can-be-more-productive-using-ai-with-ben-tossell/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aidfulai.github.io/pages/where-it-happens/how-writers-can-be-more-productive-using-ai-with-ben-tossell/</guid><description>Metadata series: Where It Happens guest: Ben Tossell release-date: 2022-11-30
Mini-summary AI will be used in advertising to modify an ad to best suited to you.
The chrome extension and desktop application bearly.ai is the currently most used AI-tool by Ben Tossell . It can reformulate, shorten, summarize and more a webpage or text input.
Search will be changed by generative AI. A first glimpse gives metaphor systems .</description></item></channel></rss>